Do I say "Stop what?"
or just throw in the towel?
(Beverley:)I don't see why I should
have to watch your father
(Beverley:)parade around with some
Bible-thumping bumpkin.
(Sheldon:)Oh, excuse me, that is my mother
you're talking about,
(Sheldon:)however accurately.
Okay, Beverly,
(Penny:)aren't you overreacting
a little?
(Penny:)All we know is they shared
a cab and had a nightcap.
(Sheldon:)And turned their phones off.
(Leonard:)Not helping, buddy.
(Leonard:)Mother, Penny and I really want
you to be part of this.
(Leonard:)Please stay.
(Penny:)Yeah, plus if you leave,
(Penny:)Alfred will know
he got under your skin.
(Beverley:)Well, we can't have that.
(Sheldon:)You know, also,
if they did have coitus,
(Sheldon:)we'll all be needing
a skilled psychiatrist.
(Raj:)It is funny
when you think about it.
(Howard:)Maybe to you.
(Howard:)You didn't get
a $500 traffic ticket.
(Bernadette:)Because you were driving
like a lunatic.
(Howard:)Hey, if thinking
secret government agents
(Howard:)are chasing you makes you
a lunatic, then... yeah, okay.